stephenfry.com 2012-12-03

# Cookie Policy « The New Adventures of Stephen Fry

SamFry Limited treats the privacy of personal information with the utmost seriousness as we realise that it is of great importance to our clients, partners and internet users alike. The information displayed here demonstrates our commitment to protecting your privacy.

This document discloses the data protection and privacy practices for SamFry Limited, including:

  * What personal information is collected
  * How we use this information
  * The choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of such information

Questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to SamFry Limited via our [contact form.](http://www.stephenfry.com/misc/contacts/)

### Information we collect 

As an advertising sales house we collect information to help define & deliver advertising solutions across our portfolio of websites.

There are 3 technologies we use to facilitate this – detailed below:

**GOOGLE ANALYTICS (GA)** **** | GA is a free service offered by Google that generates detailed statistics about the visitors to our partner websites. **All user data is entirely anonymous.**  
---|---  
**QUANTCAST (QC)** **** | QC measures web audiences, providing us with audience insights across our portfolio of sites. **All user data is entirely anonymous.**  
**SWITCH CONCEPTS (SC)** **** | SC is an adserving platform that enables us to serve & monitor display adverts across our portfolio of sites. **All user data is entirely anonymous.**  
  
Each of these services use cookie-based technology to collect information from users browsing the sites in our portfolio.

Cookies are small pieces of text stored on your computer by your web browser. They act as a memory for websites allowing them to distinguish one visitor from another. They record information about your online preferences and allow certain websites to tailor to your interests. It enables easy passage and intuitive use within certain websites.

As text a cookie is not executable. They cannot replicate themselves and they are not viruses.

For more information on what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance.

### How we use this information

The information we collect is used to help sell and deliver advertising solutions across our portfolio of websites.

The sales process requires us to gather information related to the number of users a particular site or group of sites attracts, split by geography, gender, age, & interest. We use GA & QC technology to fulfil this.

The delivery process requires us to place a client’s advert in front of an agreed number of users, an agreed number of times, over a set period of time. We use SC technology alone to achieve this.

Being able to effectively sell and deliver advertising solutions is not only core to our business, but also to that of the independent digital publishers we work with, who strive to provide a high-quality, free service to their users.

### Your choices

As demonstrated above, SamFry Limited, our publishing & technology partners take great care to protect user privacy.

We currently operate an ‘implied consent’ policy which means that by not-opting out, we assume you are happy with this usage.

If you would prefer to opt-out of any or all of these services, please follow the links below:

GOOGLE ANALYTICS http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

QUANTCAST https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out

SWITCH CONCEPTS http://www.switchconcepts.com/privacy.html

### Our right to change this policy

SamFry Limited reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will let you know at the top of this page the date it was last updated. To understand how your information will be used we encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use this web site.
